Guide to the Collection of musical autographs,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Scores
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Fidelio Overture. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (35 folios) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von "Christus am Oelberge." Oratorium., Breitkopf & Hartel: Liepzig, [n.d.], (18 folios) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Lieder von Gellert. Op. 48, no. 4. "Die Ehre Cottes in der Natur." Conductor's score and parts., [n.d.], (19 folios a.ms. fair copy, 4 pages, a.ms.bd. fair copy) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von "Gratulations Menuett." Allegretto. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (17 folios, 1 cover, 10 pages, 5 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von "Gratulations Minuet." Parts., Arthur W. Tams, Musical Library: New York, 29 August 1894, (15 pages, 1 cover) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Larghetto from the Violin Concerto, Schumann Abendlied. Score and parts., [n.d.], (26 pages a.ms.bd. fair copy, 17 folios a.ms.bd. fair copy) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Piano Concerto No. 2, op. 19. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: New York, [n.d.], (52 pages bd., 37 folios bd.) (Box 8, Folder 35)
    [With handwritten notes in score.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 4. Parts., [n.d.], (28 folios, 68 pages photocopies) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Piano Concerto No. 5 in Eflat. "Emperor" Adagio. Score and parts., [n.d.], (3 folios a.ms. fair copy, 30 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 4, op. 60., [n.d.], (38 folios) (Box 8, Folder 38)
    [Various publishers. Housed in two folders.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Mass in C Major, op. 86. Parts., [n.d.], (24 pages a.ms. fair copy, 1 folio a.ms.fair copy, 38 folios) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Adelaide, op. 46. Parts., [n.d.], (21 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Fifth Symphony. Parts (strings)., [n.d.], (19 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Fifth Symphony. Parts (winds and brass)., [n.d.], (19 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Third Symphony "Eroica." Parts for violins and viola., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (19 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Third Symphony "Eroica." Parts for cello, bass, winds, brass. Notes., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (19 folios, bd., 4 pages) (Box 9, Folder 44)
    [Organizational notes not by Seidl.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 2. Parts: strings., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (17 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Second Symphony. Parts: winds and brass., [v.p.], [n.d.], (29 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Beehoven, L.v. Sonata in G, P61.9. Parts., Konig, Trauernicht & Co.: St. Louis MO, [n.d.], (25 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Beethvoven, L.v. Moonlight Sonata. Parts., Hawkes & Co.: London, [n.d.}, (34 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 48)
    [With handwritten notes. Extra parts written in copyist's hand.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Sonata for Violincello and Piano No. 5. Op. 102, no. 2. Score and parts, [n.d.], (30 pages bd. fair copy, 35 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 49)
    [In copyist's hand. With handwritten notes. ]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Septet Op. 20. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (15 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 50)
    [With handwritten notes. Bindings deteriorated.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Serenade Op. 8. Parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (30 folios bd.) (Box 9, Folder 51)
    [Some fair copies of printed parts.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Die Ruinen von Athen "Turkish March." Parts., [n.d.], (66 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 9, Folder 52)
    [In copyist's hand. With notes.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Variations aus der Choppantasie. Score and parts., [n.d.], (8 pages a.ms.bd. fair copy, 27 a.ms. fair copy) (Box 10, Folder 54)
    [With handwritten notes. Handwritten parts in copyist's hand.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Coriolan Overture, Op. 62. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (35 pages ) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von "Die Weihe des Hauses," Overture, op. 124. Parts., [n.d.], (38 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von First Edition: "Wellington's Seige" op. 91. Score and parts with printed Beethoven statement., Wein, 1815, (4 pages bd., 35 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 57)
    [REMOVED TO VAULT.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von "Wellington's Seige." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (17 folios bd., 4 pages bd. fair copy) (Box 10, Folder 58)
    [Handwritten part in copyist's hand.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 8, op. 93 (incomplete). Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (43 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 59)
    [With handwritten notes. Housed in two folders.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 8. Parts for winds and brass only., [n.d.], (13 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 60)
    [With handwritten notes. Different edition from previous listed, Box 10/Folder ..]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 7. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (50 pages bd. (binding deteriorated), 39 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 6, op. 868. Parts. Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (35 folios bd.) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Berlioz, Hector "Les Troyens. (Marche Troyenne) Parts., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (35 folios bd.) (Box 11, Folder 63)
    [With handwritten notes. Score no longer included in collection.]
  - Berlioz, Hector "Herold en Italie" Symphonie. Score., Detmold Germany, 1874, (154 pages a.ms.s.bd. fair copy) (Box 11, Folder 64)
    [Copyist's signature: Muller. With handwritten notes.]
  - Berlioz, Hector "Herold Symphony in Four Parts." Parts., [n.d.], (20 folios a.ms. fair copy, 22 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 11, Folder 65)
    [In copyist's hand. Housed in two folders.]
  - Berlioz, Hector "Damnation des Faust" (Danse des sylphes). Parts., [n.d.], (23 folios bd., 1 folio a.ms. fair copy.) (Box 11, Folder 66)
    [With handwritten notes. Score no longer part of collection.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 8. Parts., Tams Music Library: New York, [n.d.], (22 folios bd. ) (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 9, Op. 126 in D minor. "Choral Symphony." Parts including vocals., [n.d.], (55 folios ) (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Egmont Overture, op. 84. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (36 folios bd.) (Box 11, Folder 69)
    [With handwritten changes.]
  - Bizet, Georges "Roma." Parts., [v.p.], [n.d.], (34 folios bd.) (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Bizet, Georges "Egyptian Dance" from "Djamilah.", [v.p.], [n.d.], (37 folios, 12 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 12, Folder 71)
    [With handwritten notes. ]
  - Bizet, Georges "Carmen." Suite No. 2. Score and parts., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (70 pages bd., 8 folios a.ms. fair copy, 34 folios bd.) (Box 12, Folder 72)
    [With handwritten notes. Housed in three folders.]
  - Berlioz, Hector Symphonie Fantastique. Parts., Tams Witmark: New York, [n.d.], (22 folios bd.) (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Berlioz, Hector "Marche Marocaine." Parts., Aug. Cranz: Hamburg, [n.d.], (50 parts, 2 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Berlioz, Hector Symphonie Descriptive. Parts., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (26 folios, 3 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 12, Folder 75)
    [With handwritten notes. Score no longer with collection.]
  - Berlioz, Hector "Le Menuet des Follets." Parts., Richault: Paris, [n.d.], (30 folios, 2 folio a.ms. fair copy) (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Berlioz, Hector "Romeo et Juliette" Op. 17. IV. Scherzo. Parts., G. Schirmer: New York, [n.d.], (30 folios) (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Borodin, A. "On the Steppes of Central Asia." Parts., Leipzig, [n.d.], (42 pages) (Box 13, Folder 78)
    [With handwritten notes. Score no longer in collection.]
  - Bourgault-Ducoudray, L.A. "L'Enterrement d'Ophelie: Piece pour Orchestre." Score and parts., Maquet: Paris, [n.d.], (11 pages bd., 34 folios, 3 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Boildieu A. Jean de Paris Overture. Parts., Paris and Mainz, [n.d.], (27 folios, 26 folios) (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Boieldieu Johann von Paris "Fantasie." Parts., [n.d.], (34 folios, 1 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Boldieu, F.A. "Jean de Paris." Parts., Bonn, 1762, (30 folios) (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Bochsa, P.F. "Erin's Bardic Effusions." Parts., Tams Music Library: New York9, [n.d.], (16 folios a.ms.fair copy, 1 folio) (Box 13, Folder 83)
    [Copyist's initials "V.S."]
  - Boccherini Minue du Quintette. Score and parts., Tams Witmark Music Library: New York, [n.d.}, (4 pages bd., 27 folios bd.) (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Boccherini Menuett. Score and parts., [n.d.], (2 pages a.ms.s. fair copy, 13 pages a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 13, Folder 85)
    [Copyist's intial "C." 1740?]
  - Boekelman, B. Ballabile. Score and parts., Schuberth & Co.: New York, [n.d.], (38 pages bd., 36 folios ) (Box 13, Folder 86)
    [Unsigned inscription to Seidl on cover.]
  - Boekelman, B. Ballabile. Score and parts., Schuberth & Co.: New York, [n.d.], (4 pages bd., 15 folios ) (Box 13, Folder 87)
    [Filed separately from previous entry.]
  - Blockx, J. "Milenka: La Kermesse." Parts., [n.d.], (45 folios) (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Bizet, Georges "L'Arlesienne." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (45 folios, 14 pages photocopies) (Box 13, Folder 89)
    [With pencil changes. Housed in two folders.]
  - Bizet, Georges "L'Arlesienne" Second Suite. Parts., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (40 folios) (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Bizet, Georges "Carmen." First Suite. Parts., [n.d.], (27 folios, 5 folios a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 13, Folder 91)
    [With notes in pencil. Copyist's intials V.S.]
  - Bizet, Georges "Carmen." Theatre de L'opera Comique. Parts with vocals., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (34 folios) (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Bizet, Georges "Flowersong." Score and parts., Choudens: Paris, [n.d.], (19 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 36 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 13, Folder 93)
    [With notes in pencil. Copyist's signature "V.S." appears on some.]
  - Brahms, Johanness "Symphonie No. 2." Parts., Leipzig, [n.d.], (5 folios, 53 pages photocopies) (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Brahms, Johannes Serenade in D. [n.d.], (41 folios, 1 folio a.ms. fair copy) (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Brahms, Johannes "Ungarische Tanze." Score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (80 pages bd. 43 folios) (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Brahms, Johannes "Hungarian Dances": No. 2 and No. 7. Score and parts., Simrock: Leipzig, [n.d.], (34 pages bd., 32 folios) (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Brahms, Johannes "Hungarian Dances, No. 1, 2, and 3. Score (3 copies) and parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (3 vol. bd., 39 folios) (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Brahms, Johannes Concerto for Violin and Cello Concerto. Parts, [n.d.], (42 folios) (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Borodin, A. March: Prince Igor. Score and parts. Decorative covers., St. Petersburg: Buttner, [n.d.], (38 pages bd., 45 folios, 1 folio a.ms. fair copy, 2 pages ) (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Borodin, A. Prince Igor: Opera Overture. Score and parts., [n.d.], (35 folios, 30 folios photocopies, 1 folios a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 14, Folder 101)
    [With pencil changes. Signed by copyist V.S.]
  - Brahms, Johaness Third Symphony, op. 90. Parts., [n.d.], (35 folios) (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Brahms Johannes Symphony in C, Op. 68. Parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (52 folios) (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Brahms Johannes Symphony in D, Opus 73. Parts., [n.d.], (24 folios) (Box 15, Folder 104)
    [With handwritten notes. Housed in two folders]
  - Brahms, Johannes Symphony No. 1, Op. 68. Parts., [n.d.], (42 folios, 8 folios photocopies, 81 pages photocopies) (Box 15, Folder 105)
    [Published folios extremely deteriorated. With handwritten notes. Random pages of photocopies contain single sheets previously misfiled. Housed in two folders.]
  - Brahms, Johannes Variations on a theme by Haydn. Score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (83 pages bd., 38 folios) (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Brahms, Johannes Fourth Symphony in E minor. Score and parts., Tams-Witmark Music Library: New York, [n.d.], (113 pages bd., 67 folios bd.) (Box 16)
    [With notes in pencil. Housed in four folders.]
  - Brahms, Johannes Symphony No. 3, op. 90. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartels: Leipzig, [n.d.], (50 folios, 3 folios photocopies, 1 folio a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Brahms, Johannes Symphony No. 4. Parts., Tams-Witmark: New York, [n.d.], (47 folios ) (Box 16, Folder 109)
    [With notes in pencil. Housed in 3 folders.]
  - Delibes, Leo Coppelia Suite (Ballet). Score and parts., [n.d.], (12 pages bd., 46 folios 2 folios, a.ms.s. fair copy ) (Box 17, Folder 110)
    [With handwritten notes. Housed in four boxes.]
  - Cui "Tarantella." Parts., [n.d.], (39 folios, 4 pages a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Cui "Prisonnier du Caucase." Danses circassiennes. Parts. [n.d.], (49 folios a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 17, Folder 112)
    [Copyist's signature "V.S." ]
  - Bruch, Max "Enleitung Loreley." Parts., [n.d.], (23 parts, 14 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Bruch, Max Symphony No. 1, Op. 26 in E flat., London, [n.d.], (36 parts) (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Bruch, Max Wettspiele zu Ehren des Patroklus, Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (45 folios) (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Bruch, Max "Die Loreley," introduction. Op. 16, Tams' Musical Library: New York, [n.d.], (41 folios, 11 pages) (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Dvorak, Anton Symphony in D, op. 60. Director's score and parts., Tams' Music Library: New York, [n.d.], (1 folio, bd., 37 parts) (Box 18, Folder 117)
    [Housed in two folders.]
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavische Rhapsodie." Director's score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (2 vol., bd. 33 folios, 2 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 18, Folder 118)
    [In copyist's hand.]
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavische Tanze." Director's score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, 1878, (1 vol. bd., 49 parts) (Box 18, Folder 119)
  - Delibes, Leo "Coppelia." Valse de la poupee et Csardas. Director's score and parts., (39 parts) (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Delibes, Leo "La Source." Conductor's score and parts., Paris, [n.d.], (13 pages bd. 27 folios bd., 2 folios bd. a.ms. fair copy) (Box 18, Folder 121)
    [Manuscript in copyist's hand.]
  - Delibes, Leo "Naila" Intermezzo. Parts, Berlin, 1878, (40 pages, 2 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 18, Folder 122)
    [Conductor's score no longer part of collection.]
  - Delibes, Leo "Coppelia" (Suite). Conductor's score and parts, Furstner: Berlin, [n.d.], (12 pages bd., 37 parts, 1 part incomplete) (Box 18, Folder 123)
    [Housed in two folders]
  - Delibes, Leo "Sylvia" Ballet suite. Parts., Paris, [n.d.], (37 folios, 2 folios a.ms. fair copy) (Box 18, Folder 124)
  - Dvorak, Anton Symphony No. 6, opus 96 in E minor. Parts, Hartel: New York, 1894, (38 folios) (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Dvorak, Anton Suite, op. 39. Parts. Mimeographed copies of concert announcement., (31 folios, 1 folio a.ms.fair copy, 9 pages photocopies) (Box 19, Folder 126)
    [Score no longer part of collection.]
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavonische Rhapsodien," Op. 45, no. 1. Parts., Leipzig, [n.d.], (44 folios) (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavonic Rhapsodie." Op. 45, no. 3. Parts., Hannover, [n.d.], (46 folios) (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavische Rhapsodien," Op. 45, no. 2. Parts, (53 folios, 11 pages photocopies) (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Das Golden Spinnard.", Simrock: Berlin, 1896, (48 folios) (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Der Wassermann." Opus 107. Parts., Simrock: Berlin, 1896, (55 folios) (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Dvorak, Anton "New Slavonische Tanze." Parts. Leipzig, [n.d.], (39 parts) (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Dvorak, Anton "In Der Natur." Overture, op. 91. Score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, 1894, (91 pages bd., 37 folios) (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Die Mittagshefe." Opus 108. Parts., (43 folios, 2 photocopies of folios) (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Dvorak, Anton Otello Overture. Op. 93. Score and parts., Tams' Musical Library: New York, (75 pages bd., 35 folios) (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Dvorak, Anton Carneval Overture. Parts., Simrock: Berlin, 1894, (65 folios) (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Gluck, C.W. "Iphigenie en Aulide." Overture. Score and parts., [n.d.], (38 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 39 folios a.ms.s., 1 folio) (Box 20, Folder 137)
    [In copyist's hand "V.S."]
  - Gluck, C.W. "Alceste." Copies of bass vocal part., Breitkopf and Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (16 folios bd.) (Box 20, Folder 138)
    [Numbered 1282/1284. Copies appear to be published from handwritten score. ]
  - Gluck, C.W. "Orpheus Furientanz." Parts., Hamburg, [n.d.], (27 folios a.ms.s. fair copy, 10 folios) (Box 20, Folder 139)
    [Copyist's initials "V.S." Piano score no longer part of collection.]
  - Gluck, C.W. "Armide." Overture. Parts., (20 folios a.m.s. fair copy) (Box 20, Folder 140)
  - Glinka, M.J. "Souvenir d'une nuit d'ete a Madrid." Parts., (43 folios ) (Box 20, Folder 141)
  - Glinka, M.J. "Cappriccio brillante.", Schott's: Sohne, [n.d.], (46 folios) (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - Glinka, M.J. "Kamarinskaja" Fantasie. Parts., Berlin, [n.d.], (40 pages bd., 37 parts) (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - Glinka, M.J. "Capriccio brillante." Score and parts., (60 pages a.ms., 35 parts, 7 folios a.ms.s.) (Box 20, Folder 143)
    [Handwritten in copyist's hand "V.S." ]
  - Glazunov Mazurka. Conductor's score and parts., Leipzig, [n.d.], (37 parts) (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - Glazunov Overture sur des themes greces." Op. 6. Parts., (50 parts) (Box 21, Folder 145)
  - Dvorak, Anton Symphony No. 4 in G major. Op. 88. Parts., Ewer & Co.: New York, 1892, (31 folios, 15 folios photocopies, 7 pages photocopies) (Box 20, Folder 144)
    [With pencil changes. Housed in three folders.]
  - Gluck, C.W. Ballet music. Parts., (50 parts) (Box 21, Folder 145)
    [Marked "Edition Peters."]
  - Gluck, C.W. Ballet Music "Paris and Helena." Conductor's score in 3 parts: "Sinfonia," "Presto," and "Paris and Helena.", Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, 1875, (22 pages bd., 10 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 12 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 1 hardback cover.) (Box 21, Folder 146)
    [Copyist unsigned. Handwritten notes. Binding on cover broken.]
  - Gluck, C.W. "Iphigenia in Aulis" Overture. Score and parts., [v.p.] New York, Bonn, [n.d.], (22 pages bd., 59 parts, 7 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 21, Folder 147)
    [Copyist signature "V.S." Housed in two folders.]
  - Godard, Benjamin "Jocelyn Berceuse." Piano score and parts., Choudens: Paris, (4 pages bd., 11 parts, 10 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 21, Folder 148)
    [Copyist's signature "D.S."]
  - Hartmann, E. "Nordische Volstanze." Parts., Druck & Meier: Berlin, [n.d.], (42 parts) (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Haydn, F.J. Mass No. 2. Parts., (27, parts 20, parts a.ms. ) (Box 21, Folder 150)
    [Approximate counts: some folios incomplete. Copyist's work unsigned. Housed in two folders.]
  - Haydn, F.J. Parts for multiple symphonies., [v.p.], [n.d.], (50 parts, 3 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 21, Folder 151)
    [Parts from different symphonies previously filed together (?). Symphony No. 2 and No. 14; "Breitkopf Symphony No. 96." Signed by "D.C."]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony B. 52 in C minor. Parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (21 parts) (Box 21, Folder 152A)
    [Renumbered due to cataloguing error.]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No 12. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (25 parts) (Box 21, Folder 152B)
    [With handwritten notes. Renumbered due to cataloguing error.]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 7. Parts., [n.d.], (10 parts, 4 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 21, Folder 153)
    [Copyist's signatures "V.S." and "M.D.C."]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 19. Parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (29 parts, 2 parts a.ms.s.) (Box 21, Folder 154)
    [With notes in pencil. Copyist's signature "V.S."]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony B.83. G minor, "La Poule." Parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (24 parts) (Box 22, Folder 155)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony B. 84, E-flat. Score and parts, Winterthur-Biedermann: Leipzig, (1 vol. bd., 25 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 156)
    [In copyist's hand, unsigned.]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony 21. B. 85, B-flat. "La Reine." Score and parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (23 parts) (Box 22, Folder 157)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony B.92. G major. "Oxford." Parts., [n.d.], (26 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 158)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony 10. B. 86. D major. Parts., Simrock: Bonn and Breitkopf & Hartl: Leipzig, [n.d.], (27 parts, 3 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 2. Parts, [n.d.], (28 parts, 3 parts a.ms.) (Box 22, Folder 160)
    [Library folder designates the work as "L'Curs, C Major." ]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B. 87, A major. Parts., Bonn: Simrock, [n.d.], (23 parts) (Box 22, Folder 161)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 4. Parts., [n.d.], (20 parts, 14 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 162)
    [Library folder designates work " B. 101.]
  - Gounod, C.F. "Cinq-Mars." Sarabande. Parts., (36 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 163)
  - Gounod, Berceuse "Clos ta Paupiere." Score and parts., (6 pages bd., 5 parts, 10 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 164)
  - Gounod, C. "Mirella" Overture. Score and parts., Tams Musical Library: New York, 13 February 1895, (14 pages a.ms. bd. fair copy, 34 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - Gounod, C. "Der Tribut von Zamora." Parts., [n.d.]`, (36 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy ) (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - Grieg, Edvard Herzwunden, Op. 34. Score and parts., (7 pages bd., 21 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - Grieg, Edvard Piano Concerto, A minor. Parts., Tams Music Library: New York, [n.d.], (8 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 22, Folder 168)
  - Grieg, Edvard "Norwegian Melodies." Score and parts., Peters: Leipzig, [n.d.], (15 pages bd., 18 parts) (Box 22, Folder 169)
  - Handel, F.J. Overture to the Occasional Oratoria. Score and parts., [n.d.], (26 parts, 1 vol. a.ms. bd., 1 part a.ms.s fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 170)
    [Fair copy of score appears unfinished.]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 12. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (37 parts) (Box 23, Folder 171)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 4. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartl: New York, [n.d.], (12 parts) (Box 23, Folder 172)
  - Haydn, F.J. "Trauersymphonie, No. 44." Parts., [n.d.], (23 parts) (Box 23, Folder 173)
  - Haydn, F.J Ouverture: "Die Jahreszeiten." P. 61. Parts., [n.d.], (20 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 174)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B. 44 in Eminor, "Trauer." Parts. Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (21 parts) (Box 23, Folder 175)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B.82. C major, "L'ours." Parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (25 parts) (Box 23, Folder 176)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B. 98, Bflat. Parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (28 parts) (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B. 94. G major. "Paukenschlag." Parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (29 parts) (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony No. 2. Parts., [n.d.], (3 parts) (Box 23, Folder 179)
    [All violincello and bass parts. ]
  - Haydn, F.J. Symphony. B. 45, E minor. "Abschied." Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (19 pages bd., 14 folios bd.) (Box 23, Folder 180)
  - Haydn, F.J. Serenade. Score and parts., [n.d.], (4 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 11 parts, 9 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 181)
  - Handel, F.J. Motets. Parts., [n.d.], (25 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 182)
    [Copyist's initials V.S.]
  - Humperdinck, Englebert "Hansel und Gretel." Score., Schott's Sohne: Mainz, [n.d.], (28 pages bd. ) (Box 23, Folder 183)